那是谁
Who was that?
辩方律师  没什么要紧事
Aw, just some defense attorney; nothing important.
-艾丽西娅  有点问题  -怎么了
- We have a problem, Alicia. - What is it?
[其他费用]
"Other expenses."
克拉克提醒我的
Clarke brought this to my attention.
财务状况声明  斯威尼作假了
The financial disclosure statement-- Sweeney lied.
他把所有娱乐开销都放进去了
He put all his recreational expenses in it.
娱乐
Recreational?
-毒品  性理疗  -上帝
- Drugs and sexual therapy. - Oh, dear Lord.
对  他可能因此被捕  艾丽西娅
Yeah, he could get arrested for this, Alicia.
145,000美元呢
It's $145,000.
我能划掉合同上的金额吗
Okay, well, uh, can I cross out the amount on the contract?
可以  然后让他签名
Yes. And get him to initial it.
然后让他退14万5千块
And have him refund $145,000
到他的商务账户
into his business account,